Priyanka kamlakar kakde () Featured

Associate Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Client Management, Technical Architecture, SAP Implementation, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, XML



Current Designation: Associate Consultant - IT Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Current Company: TAMS Infotech Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Consultant, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement

Gathering, System Analysis, Client Management, Technical Architecture, SAP

Implementation, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, XML

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

An Engineering Graduate with 2.6 years of SAPUI5 Mobile Application Development Experience. Expert in translating business requirements into technical solutions (requirement gathering and providing integrated SAP Fiori solution).

Great understanding of the customer requirement and able to demonstrate the process flow with good communication and coding skills.

Experienced in SAP application development by using SAPUI5 technology.

Sound Knowledge of ODATA, Standard Odata activation.

Experienced in FIORI Launchpad configuration (Role, Catalog, Group, and Tile).

Willingness and ability to quickly adapt to new environment.

Experienced in website development by using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, and Ajax.

Work Experience

TAMS Infotech as Associate Consultant - IT Jul 2019 to Till Date

* P n L And Balance sheet report(Jul 2020 - till)

Environment: SAP Fiori using Eclipse

Description: PnL And Balance sheet report application is a full screen application of TAMS. Main functionality in this application is displaying the financial Report of profit and loss And Balance sheet, schedule profit and loss, schedule balance sheet on the basis of company code reporting fiscal year and comparison fiscal year

User can select the request Icon tab and get the details page accordingly.

Role: SAPUI5 Developer

Responsibilities: Developed the application as per own understanding and internal requirement. Worked with backend team and gave them the frontend necessity, implemented all the functionalities in frontend and developed the Application using JavaScript, XML, HTML, CSS and etc.

Asset Manager Cipla(Desc 2019 - Jun 2020)

Environment: SAP Asset manager using WebIDE

Description: Asset Manager is designed to automate workflow and improve service

with mobile work orders, notifications and time management. Asset Manager connects mobile

1/22/2021

employees with the data stored in an SAP system so they can better manage work and service requests.

The Asset Manager client is the component that the end user will have to work with. The client runs on the Mobile device used to track your work.

When new order are entered into the Asset Manager client, the client saves this information on the Mobile device. A transmit must be performed to update the SAP ECC with the new information. A transmit is a connection between the Mobile device and a component of Asset Manager called the server. The server will connect to the Asset Manager database and update it with the new information entered on the handheld device. The server will also download any new information from the SAP ERP database and pass it back to your handheld device.

Asset Manager extends the following SAP ERP functionality to mobile devices:

Displaying work orders and their details

Editing work orders and their details

Creating work orders and their details

Role: SAPUI Developer Responsibilities:

Development of Frontend using WebIDE.

Process understanding

Following Assetmanager Standard and do custom development

HZL Fiori Barcode implementation:(Jun2019 - Nov2019)

Environment: SAP Fiori using Eclipse

Description: Developed 14 custom Fiori applications for different business processes. Main functionality of this application is to scan barcode using inbuilt scanner of tablet and work on that scanned material as create GRN, Quality analysis of material, Quality pending and rejected status of material and so on, also implemented the voice search functionality in Launchpad.

Scan barcode using inbuilt scanner of tablet

Upload Excel file and display that data in table format

Add voice search functionality in Launchpad

Role: SAPUI5 Developer

Klouddata Labs as Associate Consultant

Feb 2018 to May 2019

Employee Timesheet (Internal Project):(march 2019 - May2019)

Environment: SAP Fiori using Eclipse

Description:

Employee Timesheet is an internal application for Employee. Using this app, employee. can fill up their daily timesheet (choose the project and Task from the drop down).

They can also enter date, total working hours and description and sub task. All fields are mandatory. After submitting a task will be created. Employee can download Timesheet in Both excel and pdf format. A Calendar is given and every date color changes as per the working hours (ex: if working hours is less than 8 hrs then its turn red).

Employee can submit and download Timesheet.

Calendar date colors change as per working hours.

Role: SAPUI5 Develop

Responsibilities:Developed the application as per own understanding and internal requirement. Worked with backend team and gave them the frontend necessity, implemented all the

functionalities in frontend and developed the Application using JavaScript, XML, HTML, CSS and etc.

* GRC Compleance Approver(Jan2019 - Feb 2019)

Environment: SAP Fiori

Description: SAP standard GRC Compliance Approver Application Extension

Responsibilities: Extension of standard application considering all the standard extension rules and add two custom Icon Tab.

* Post Parked Document (Sep 2018 - Dec2018)

Environment: SAP Fiori using Eclipse

Description: Post Parked Document is a full screen application of HZL. Main functionality of this application is to show the document list which is based on Company code, document no. and fiscal year. User will get the details only after submitting mandatory details. User can edit some details, add comments and download document .pdf file.

Role: SAPUI5 Developer

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Pune University in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
SAP : SAP FIORI , SAPUI5			
JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3			
Jquery, Ajax, JSON, XML			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Maithili				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time